NYS PERB Agreements 5140
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- College and University: Finger Lakes Community College through Hudson Valley Community College (Box 261)
  - Fulton Montgomery Community, 1971-1982 (Box 261, Folder 6)
  - Genesee Community College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 261, Folder 7)
  - Genesee Community College, 1996-2003 (Box 261, Folder 8)
  - Genesee Comm. College, 1990-1991 (Box 261, Folder 9)
  - Genesee Community College 72-76, 1972-1976 (Box 261, Folder 10)
  - Herkimer 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 261, Folder 11)
  - Herkimer County Community College, 2006 (Box 261, Folder 12)
  - Hudson Valley CC, 1986-1989 (Box 261, Folder 13)
  - Hudson Valley Community College, 1995-2003 (Box 261, Folder 14)
  - Hudson Valley Community College, 1995-2004 (Box 261, Folder 15)
  - Hudson Valley Community College 72-76, 1972-1976 (Box 261, Folder 16)
- College and University: Jamestown Community College through Jefferson Community College (Box 262)
  - Jamestown Community College, 1991-1997 (Box 262, Folder 1)
  - Hudson Valley Community College, 1969-1994 (Box 262, Folder 2)
  - Jamestown CC, 1987-1994 (Box 262, Folder 3)
  - Jamestown 1968-72, 1968-1972 (Box 262, Folder 4)
  - Jamestown, 1998-2003 (Box 262, Folder 5)
  - Jamestown Community College, 1973-1991 (Box 262, Folder 6)
  - Jefferson Comm. College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 262, Folder 7)
  - Jefferson Comm. College, 1995-2003 (Box 262, Folder 8)
  - Jefferson Community College, 2001-2004 (Box 262, Folder 9)
  - Jefferson Community College 72-76, 1972-1976 (Box 262, Folder 10)
- College and University: Long Island University through Nassau Community College (Box 263)
  - Long Island University (The Brooklyn Center), 1972-1976 (Box 263, Folder 1)
  - Long Island Univ., 1988-1998 (Box 263, Folder 2)
  - Long Island University, 1994-2000 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Long Island University, 2000-2006 (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Mohawk 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 263, Folder 5)
  - Mohawk Valley Community College, 1995-1999 (Box 263, Folder 6)
  - Mohawk Valley Community College 72-76, 1972-1976 (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Mohawk Valley Comm. College, 1986-1993 (Box 263, Folder 8)
  - Mohawk Valley Community College, 1996-2000 (Box 263, Folder 9)
  - Monroe CC, 1987-1990 (Box 263, Folder 10)
  - Monroe Community College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 263, Folder 11)
  - Monroe Community College, 1999-2003 (Box 263, Folder 12)
  - Monroe Community College, 2002 (Box 263, Folder 13)
  - Nassau Community College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 263, Folder 14)
  - Nassau Community College, 1995-2005 (Box 263, Folder 15)
  - Nassau Community College, 1991-1995 (Box 263, Folder 16)
  - Nassau Community College 72-76, 1971-1983 (Box 263, Folder 17)
- College and University: New York, City University of through Onondaga Community College (Box 264)
  - New York Institute of Technology 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - New York, State University of, 1971-1982 (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - N.Y.U., 1987-1990 (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Newark College of Engineering 72-76, 1972-1976 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - Niagara County Comm. Col. 68-72, 1969-1973 (Box 264, Folder 5)
  - Niagara County Community Col. 1972-1985, 1973-1994 (Box 264, Folder 6)
  - Niagara Community College, 1985-1998 (Box 264, Folder 7)
  - Niagara CCC, 1987-1996 (Box 264, Folder 8)
  - Niagara County Community College, 1996-2002 (Box 264, Folder 9)
  - Essex Cntg. Franklin County + North Country Community College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 264, Folder 10)
  - North Country Community College 72-76, 1972-1976 (Box 264, Folder 11)
  - North Country Community College 72-76, 1972-1976 (Box 264, Folder 12)
  - North Country Community College, 1994-1997 (Box 264, Folder 13)
  - North Country Comm. College, 1985-1990 (Box 264, Folder 14)
  - North Country Comm. College, 1990-1994 (Box 264, Folder 15)
  - Onondaga Community College, 1996-2000 (Box 264, Folder 16)
  - Onondaga Community College 72-76, 1972-1976 (Box 264, Folder 17)
  - Onondaga Community College, 1972-1996 (Box 264, Folder 18)
  - Onondaga Community College, 1987-2000 (Box 264, Folder 19)
  - Onondaga Community College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 264, Folder 20)
- College and University: Orange County Community College through Suffolk Community College (Box 265)
  - Orange Country Community College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - Orange County Community College, 1991 (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Orange County Comm. College, 1982-1997 (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - Orange County CC, 1982-1994 (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Ontario County Comm. College, 1988-1991 (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - Pratt Institute, 1981-1992 (Box 265, Folder 6)
  - Rockland Community College, 1997-2001 (Box 265, Folder 7)
  - Rockland Community College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 265, Folder 8)
  - Rockland Community College 72-76, 1972-1976 (Box 265, Folder 9)
  - St. John's University 72-76, 1972-1976 (Box 265, Folder 10)
  - Schenectady Community College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 265, Folder 11)
  - Schenectady Community, 1991-1999 (Box 265, Folder 12)
  - Schenectady County Community College, 1999-2004 (Box 265, Folder 13)
  - Schenectady County Comm. College, 1988-1991 (Box 265, Folder 14)
  - Schenectady Community Col., 1976-1994 (Box 265, Folder 15)
  - State University of New York, 1979-1982 (Box 265, Folder 16)
  - State University Construction Find, 1985-1988 (Box 265, Folder 17)
  - Suffolk County Community College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 265, Folder 18)
  - Suffolk County Community College, 1997-2001 (Box 265, Folder 19)
- College and University: Suffolk Community College through Westchester Community College (Box 266)
  - Suffolk County, 1974-1984 (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - Suffolk CC, 1984-1988 (Box 266, Folder 2)
  - Suffolk County Community College, 1987-2005 (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Sullivan, 1969-1987 (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Sullivan Community College, 1992-2004 (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - Sullivan County CC, 1987-1992 (Box 266, Folder 6)
  - Sullivan County CC, 1987-1990 (Box 266, Folder 7)
  - Syracuse University 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 266, Folder 8)
  - Tompkins - Cortland Community College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 266, Folder 9)
  - Tompkins - Cortland Comm. College, 1997-2004 (Box 266, Folder 10)
  - Tompkins + Cortland Comm. College, 1988-1990 (Box 266, Folder 11)
  - Tompkins Cortland Community College, 1995-1998 (Box 266, Folder 12)
  - Tompkins - Cortland Comm. College, 1982-1996 (Box 266, Folder 13)
  - Ulster Co. Comm. College, 1990-1994 (Box 266, Folder 14)
  - Ulster Comm. College, 1997-2004 (Box 266, Folder 15)
  - Ulster County Community College, 2002 (Box 266, Folder 16)
  - Ulster County. Community Col. 72-89, 1972-1989 (Box 266, Folder 17)
  - Washtenaw Community College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 266, Folder 18)
  - Ulster County Community College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 266, Folder 19)
  - Westchester County Community College, 1985-1992 (Box 266, Folder 20)
  - Westchester Community College 68-72, 1968-1972 (Box 266, Folder 21)
  - Westchester Comm. College, 1992-1993 (Box 266, Folder 22)
  - Westchester Community College, 1995-2002 (Box 266, Folder 23)
- Fire and Police: Albany through Amityville (Box 267)
  - Albany, 1992-1995 (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - Albany (Firemen), 1970-1977 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - Albany (Police), 1975-1980 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - Albany (City), 1992-1993 (Box 267, Folder 4)
  - Albany's (Counties), 1991-2003 (Box 267, Folder 5)
  - Albany, 1986-1995 (Box 267, Folder 6)
  - Albion, 1971-1989 (Box 267, Folder 7)
  - Albion (Villages), 1997 (Box 267, Folder 8)
  - Albion (Police), 1970-1978 (Box 267, Folder 9)
  - Alleghany County, 1978-1992 (Box 267, Folder 10)
  - Alexandria Bay (Villages), 1999 (Box 267, Folder 11)
  - Alleghany (Co.), 1989-1994 (Box 267, Folder 12)
  - Alleghany (Countries), 1984-1997 (Box 267, Folder 13)
  - Amherst, 1991-1996 (Box 267, Folder 14)
  - Amherst (Firemen), 1975-1984 (Box 267, Folder 15)
  - Amherst (Police), 1969-1981 (Box 267, Folder 16)
  - Amityville, 1970-1978 (Box 267, Folder 17)
  - Amityville (Villages), 1968-1992 (Box 267, Folder 18)
  - Amityville (Police), 1985 (Box 267, Folder 19)
  - Amityville (Police), 1974 (Box 267, Folder 20)
- Fire and Police: Amsterdam through Bath (Box 268)
  - Amsterdam, 1986-1987 (Box 268, Folder 1)
  - Amsterdam (City), 1994-1995 (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - Amsterdam (Police + Firemen), 1982-1993 (Box 268, Folder 3)
  - Angola, 1984-1986 (Box 268, Folder 4)
  - Ardsley, 1998 (Box 268, Folder 5)
  - Arlington, 1989-1990 (Box 268, Folder 6)
  - Asharohen (Police), 1988-1993 (Box 268, Folder 7)
  - Asharoken (Police), 1975 (Box 268, Folder 8)
  - Attica, 1989-1995 (Box 268, Folder 9)
  - Auburn (Police), 1981-1991 (Box 268, Folder 10)
  - Auburn (Firemen), 1968-1974 (Box 268, Folder 11)
  - Auburn (Police), 1972 (Box 268, Folder 12)
  - Auburn (Fire + Police), 1974-1982 (Box 268, Folder 13)
  - Auburn (Firefighters), 1986-1990 (Box 268, Folder 14)
  - Auburn (Firemen), 1978-1981 (Box 268, Folder 15)
  - Avon, 1989-1997 (Box 268, Folder 16)
  - Baldwin, 1994 (Box 268, Folder 17)
  - Baldwinsville, 1987-1995 (Box 268, Folder 18)
  - Ballston Spa (villages), 1994-1996 (Box 268, Folder 19)
  - Batavia (city), 2000-2003 (Box 268, Folder 20)
  - Batavia, 1981-1985 (Box 268, Folder 21)
  - Batavia Firefighters, 1975 (Box 268, Folder 22)
  - Batavia (police), 1976 (Box 268, Folder 23)
  - Batavia, City of (Police), 1989-1994 (Box 268, Folder 24)
  - Batavia (Firemen), 1993-1995 (Box 268, Folder 25)
  - Bath (Villages), 1995-1998 (Box 268, Folder 26)
  - Bath (Police), 1987 (Box 268, Folder 27)
- Fire and Police: Beacon through Briarcliff Manor (Box 269)
  - Beacon, 1986-1988 (Box 269, Folder 1)
  - Beacon (Police), 1968 (Box 269, Folder 2)
  - Beacon (City), 1999 (Box 269, Folder 3)
  - Bedford, Town of (Police), 1978-1992 (Box 269, Folder 4)
  - Bedford, 1990-1991 (Box 269, Folder 5)
  - Bethlehem, 1974-1986 (Box 269, Folder 6)
  - Bethlehem, 1973-1990 (Box 269, Folder 7)
  - Bethlehem (Police), 1973 (Box 269, Folder 8)
  - Bethlehem, 1987-1998 (Box 269, Folder 9)
  - Binghamton (Firefighters), 1992-1995 (Box 269, Folder 9)
  - Binghamton (Firefighters), 1977 (Box 269, Folder 10)
  - Binghamton (Police), 1982-1997 (Box 269, Folder 12)
  - Binghamton, 1987-1989 (Box 269, Folder 13)
  - Binghamton, City of (Firemen), 1981-1982 (Box 269, Folder 14)
  - Binghamton, City of (Policemen), 1969-1997 (Box 269, Folder 15)
  - Binghamton (Police), 1970-1976 (Box 269, Folder 16)
  - Binghamton (Firemen), 1969-1977 (Box 269, Folder 17)
  - Blasdell (villages), 1997-2001 (Box 269, Folder 18)
  - Blasdell (Police), 1984-1986 (Box 269, Folder 19)
  - Blasdell (village of) - Police, 1970-1987 (Box 269, Folder 20)
  - Blooming Grove, 1970-1994 (Box 269, Folder 21)
  - Blooming Groves, 1988-1990 (Box 269, Folder 22)
  - Blooming Grove (Police), 1999-2001 (Box 269, Folder 23)
  - Brewster (Police), 1971-1976 (Box 269, Folder 24)
  - Brewster (Police), 1972 (Box 269, Folder 25)
  - Briancliff manor (Police), 1986-2002 (Box 269, Folder 26)
  - Braincliff manor (Police), 1969-1977 (Box 269, Folder 27)
- Fire and Police: Brighton through Buffalo (Box 270)
  - Brighton (police), 1986 (Box 270, Folder 1)
  - Brighton (firemen), 1969-1975 (Box 270, Folder 2)
  - Brighton (firemen), 1970-1974 (Box 270, Folder 3)
  - Brighton - beons, 1997-2000 (Box 270, Folder 4)
  - Brighton, 1989-1995 (Box 270, Folder 5)
  - Brockport, 1983-2003 (Box 270, Folder 6)
  - Brockport, 1989-1994 (Box 270, Folder 7)
  - Bronxville, village of (Policemen), 1968-1991 (Box 270, Folder 8)
  - Bronxville (Police), 1988-2002 (Box 270, Folder 9)
  - Broome Co. (Police), 1973-1979 (Box 270, Folder 10)
  - Broome Counties, 1982-1991 (Box 270, Folder 11)
  - Buchanan, 1980-1991 (Box 270, Folder 12)
  - Buchanan (villages), 1993 (Box 270, Folder 13)
  - Buchanan, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 14)
  - Buffalo (Firemen), 1980-1983 (Box 270, Folder 15)
  - Buffalo, City of Police, 1991 (Box 270, Folder 16)
  - Buffalo (City), 1992-1995 (Box 270, Folder 17)
  - Buffalo (Police), 1970-1978 (Box 270, Folder 18)
  - Buffalo (Firemen), 1971-1981 (Box 270, Folder 19)
- Fire and Police: Camillus through Cheektowaga (Box 271)
  - Camden (Villages), 1997 (Box 271, Folder 1)
  - Camillus, Town of, 1979-1991 (Box 271, Folder 2)
  - Camillus, 1985-1990 (Box 271, Folder 3)
  - Camillus - towns, 1994-1997 (Box 271, Folder 4)
  - Canandaigua (police), 1976-1978 (Box 271, Folder 5)
  - Canandaigua (Police), 1970-1983 (Box 271, Folder 6)
  - Canandaigua (cities), 1988-1994 (Box 271, Folder 7)
  - Canandaigua, City (Firemen), 1986-1987 (Box 271, Folder 8)
  - Canandaigua (Siermen), 1976-1977 (Box 271, Folder 9)
  - Canandaigua, 1986-1991 (Box 271, Folder 10)
  - Canton (Village), 1998-2001 (Box 271, Folder 11)
  - Canton (Police), 1975-1976 (Box 271, Folder 12)
  - Canton, village of (Police), 1987-1999 (Box 271, Folder 13)
  - Carmel (Police), 1972-1991 (Box 271, Folder 14)
  - Carmel, Town of (Policemen), 1968-1970 (Box 271, Folder 15)
  - Carmel - Boens, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 16)
  - Carthage, 1998-1999 (Box 271, Folder 17)
  - Catskill (villages), 1997 (Box 271, Folder 18)
  - Catskill (Villages), 1997 (Box 271, Folder 19)
  - Catskill Police Association, 1974-1994 (Box 271, Folder 20)
  - Catskill, 1986 (Box 271, Folder 21)
  - Cattaurgus County, 1976-1997 (Box 271, Folder 22)
  - Cattaraugus (countries), 1998-2000 (Box 271, Folder 23)
  - Cattaraugus, County of (Police + fire), 1969-1997 (Box 271, Folder 24)
  - Centre Island - Police, 1974-1977 (Box 271, Folder 25)
  - Centre Island, 1987-1989 (Box 271, Folder 26)
  - Centre Island (villages), 1989-1993 (Box 271, Folder 27)
  - Chathan, 1980-1982 (Box 271, Folder 28)
  - Chautagua - Countries, 1990-2000 (Box 271, Folder 29)
  - Cheektowaga (Police), 1982-1987 (Box 271, Folder 30)
  - Cheektowaga, 1987-1989 (Box 271, Folder 31)
  - Cheektowaga, 1990-1992 (Box 271, Folder 32)
  - Cheektowaga - Countries, 1993-1995 (Box 271, Folder 33)
  - Cheektowaga (Police), 1971-1972 (Box 271, Folder 34)
- Fire and Police: Chemung through Columbia (Box 272)
  - Chemung, County of (Police), 1978-1990 (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - Chemung - Countries (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - Chemung County - Sheriff's Association, 1977 (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - Chenango, 1989-1999 (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - Chester, 1998 (Box 272, Folder 5)
  - Chester (villages), 1997-1998 (Box 272, Folder 6)
  - Cicero (towns), 1999 (Box 272, Folder 7)
  - Clarkstown (Police), 1989-1994 (Box 272, Folder 8)
  - Clarkstown (Police), 1969-1970 (Box 272, Folder 9)
  - Clarkstown, 1986-1988 (Box 272, Folder 10)
  - Clay Police, 1979-2003 (Box 272, Folder 11)
  - Clay, 1987-1988 (Box 272, Folder 12)
  - Clinton - Countries, 1991-1996 (Box 272, Folder 13)
  - Cobleskill, 1988-1993 (Box 272, Folder 14)
  - Cobleskill (villages), 2000-2003 (Box 272, Folder 15)
  - Cohoes, City of (Policemen), 1971-1974 (Box 272, Folder 16)
  - Cohoe (cities), 1989-1994 (Box 272, Folder 17)
  - Cohoes Fire Assoc., 1975-1978 (Box 272, Folder 18)
  - Cohoes (Police), 1973-1986 (Box 272, Folder 19)
  - Cohoes, City of (Firemen), 1973-1985 (Box 272, Folder 20)
  - Cold Springs (Police), 1975-1987 (Box 272, Folder 21)
  - Cold Spring, 1992-1996 (Box 272, Folder 22)
  - Colonie (Police), 1982-1994 (Box 272, Folder 23)
  - Colonies (Towns), 2001 (Box 272, Folder 24)
  - Columbia County Sheriff's, 1991-1993 (Box 272, Folder 25)
  - Columbia - countries, 1997-2002 (Box 272, Folder 26)
  - Columbia, 1985-1995 (Box 272, Folder 27)
- Fire and Police: Cooperstown through Dix Hills (Box 273)
  - Cooperstown (Police), 1991-1997 (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - Cooperstown (Police), 1972 (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - Corning (Fire), 1971-1979 (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - Corning (Firemen), 1971-1995 (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - Corning (Firemen), 1968-1969 (Box 273, Folder 5)
  - Corning (Police), 1969-1971 (Box 273, Folder 6)
  - Corning, 1987-1989 (Box 273, Folder 7)
  - Cornwall - Police, 1970-1998 (Box 273, Folder 8)
  - Cornwall (Towns), 1995-1998 (Box 273, Folder 9)
  - Cortland (firemen), 1969-1970 (Box 273, Folder 10)
  - Cortland (cities), 1991-1992 (Box 273, Folder 11)
  - Cortland (Police), 1982-1992 (Box 273, Folder 12)
  - Cortland - countries, 1992-1993 (Box 273, Folder 13)
  - Cortland (Police), 1977 (Box 273, Folder 14)
  - Cortland - Firemen, 1975-1990 (Box 273, Folder 15)
  - Cortland (Police), 1969-1984 (Box 273, Folder 16)
  - Cortland, 1989-1991 (Box 273, Folder 17)
  - Cortland (Towns), 1997 (Box 273, Folder 18)
  - Core Neck (villages), 1989-1992 (Box 273, Folder 19)
  - Cone Neck - Police, 1974-1983 (Box 273, Folder 20)
  - Croton - on - Hudson (Policemen), 1974-1980 (Box 273, Folder 21)
  - Croton (villages), 1996-1999 (Box 273, Folder 22)
  - Dansville (Police), 1971-1975 (Box 273, Folder 23)
  - Dansville (villages), 1999 (Box 273, Folder 24)
  - Dansville, 1990 (Box 273, Folder 25)
  - Delaware - counties, 1996-1997 (Box 273, Folder 26)
  - Delhi (Villages), 2000-2004 (Box 273, Folder 27)
  - Depew (villages), 1997-2000 (Box 273, Folder 28)
  - Depew, 1974-1990 (Box 273, Folder 29)
  - Depew, 1986-1989 (Box 273, Folder 30)
  - Dewitt and PBA, 1975-1981 (Box 273, Folder 31)
  - Dewitt (towns), 1990-2001 (Box 273, Folder 32)
  - Dewitt, 1970-1990 (Box 273, Folder 33)
  - Dix Hills, 1986-1991 (Box 273, Folder 34)
- Fire and Police: Dobbs Ferry through Eastchester (Box 274)
  - Dobbs - Ferry (police), 1981-1990 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Dunkirk, 1969-1974 (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Dunkirk (Cities), 1995-1997 (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - Dunkirk, 1990-1992 (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - Dunkirk (Firefighters), 1975 (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - Dunkirk (Police), 1975-1976 (Box 274, Folder 6)
  - Dutchess, 2001-2006 (Box 274, Folder 7)
  - Dutchess, 1986-1988 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - East Aurora, 1989-1993 (Box 274, Folder 9)
  - E. Aurora, 1985-1989 (Box 274, Folder 10)
  - East Aurora (Police), 1970-1978 (Box 274, Folder 11)
  - East Aurora - Fire, 1985-1989 (Box 274, Folder 12)
  - East Fishkill (Town), 1995-1996 (Box 274, Folder 13)
  - East Fishkill, 1994 (Box 274, Folder 14)
  - East Greenbush, 1973-1981 (Box 274, Folder 15)
  - East Greenbush (Towns), 1991-1993 (Box 274, Folder 16)
  - East Hampton, 1988-1992 (Box 274, Folder 17)
  - East Hampton (Police), 1974-1981 (Box 274, Folder 18)
  - East Hampton (villages), 1993-2005 (Box 274, Folder 19)
  - East Rochester, 1990-1992 (Box 274, Folder 20)
  - East Rochester - village, 2000-2002 (Box 274, Folder 21)
  - East Rochester (Police), 1982-1994 (Box 274, Folder 22)
  - East Rochester, 1982 (Box 274, Folder 23)
  - Eastchester (towns), 1991-1993 (Box 274, Folder 24)
  - Eastchester, 1989-1990 (Box 274, Folder 25)
  - Eastchester (Police), 1977-1978 (Box 274, Folder 26)
  - Eastchester (Firemen), 1971 (Box 274, Folder 27)
  - Eastchester (fire), 1971-1975 (Box 274, Folder 28)
- Fire and Police: Eden through Fairview (Box 275)
  - Eden (Towns), 1992-1996 (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - Ellenville and PBA, 1979-1980 (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - Elmira (cities), 1991-1992 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - Elmira, City of (Firemen), 1969-1970 (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - Elmira (Firemen), 1979-1982 (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - Elmira, City of (Policemen), 1969-1970 (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - Elmira Heights, 1985-1988 (Box 275, Folder 7)
  - Elmira Heights Fire, 1971-1977 (Box 275, Folder 8)
  - Elmira Heights (Police), 1992 (Box 275, Folder 9)
  - Elmira Heights - Village, 1991-1994 (Box 275, Folder 10)
  - Elmsford - village, 1987 (Box 275, Folder 11)
  - Elmsford (Police), 1979 (Box 275, Folder 12)
  - Endicott, 1995 (Box 275, Folder 13)
  - Endicott, 1990 (Box 275, Folder 14)
  - Endicott (Firemen), 1970 (Box 275, Folder 15)
  - Endicott (Police) (Box 275, Folder 16)
  - Endicott, Village of (Policemen), 1968-1971 (Box 275, Folder 17)
  - Endicott, Village of (Policemen), 1972-1975 (Box 275, Folder 18)
  - Endicott (Firefighters), 1978-1991 (Box 275, Folder 19)
  - Erie (Co.) Sheriffs Dept., 1982-1994 (Box 275, Folder 20)
  - Erie County (Police), 1968 (Box 275, Folder 21)
  - Evans (Town), 1960-1961 (Box 275, Folder 22)
  - Evans, Town of Police, 1987-1992 (Box 275, Folder 23)
  - Evans, 1986 (Box 275, Folder 24)
  - Evans, 1985-1986 (Box 275, Folder 25)
  - Fairport, 1991 (Box 275, Folder 26)
  - Fairports (villages), 1998-2001 (Box 275, Folder 27)
  - Fairport and Fairport Police Billy Club, 1993 (Box 275, Folder 28)
  - Fairview, 1988-1990 (Box 275, Folder 29)
  - Fairview Fire Dist. + Local 2623, IAFF, 1999-2001 (Box 275, Folder 30)
  - Fairview, 1979-1985 (Box 275, Folder 31)
- Fire and Police: Falconer through Fulton (Box 276)
  - Falconer and PBA, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 1)
  - Fallsburg, 1987 (Box 276, Folder 2)
  - Fallsburg (Town), 1992 (Box 276, Folder 3)
  - Fallsburg, 1993-1994 (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - Fayetteville and PBA, 1977-1978 (Box 276, Folder 5)
  - Fishkill, 1988-1995 (Box 276, Folder 6)
  - Floral Park, Village of (Policemen), 1994-1997 (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - Floral Park, 1991 (Box 276, Folder 8)
  - Fort Edward and PBA, 1991-1994 (Box 276, Folder 9)
  - Fort Plain + PBA, 1980-1990 (Box 276, Folder 10)
  - Frankfort - Police, 1982-1986 (Box 276, Folder 11)
  - Frankfurt (Villages), 1988-2002 (Box 276, Folder 12)
  - Frankfurt - towns, 1992 (Box 276, Folder 13)
  - Franklin - countries, 1995-1997 (Box 276, Folder 14)
  - Fredonia - Fire, 1990-1995 (Box 276, Folder 15)
  - Fredonia, village of (Police), 1978-1983 (Box 276, Folder 16)
  - Fredonia, 1987-1990 (Box 276, Folder 17)
  - Freeport (Policemen), 1974-1994 (Box 276, Folder 18)
  - Freeport (Police), 1973-1975 (Box 276, Folder 19)
  - Fulton (Firemen), 1976-1981 (Box 276, Folder 20)
  - Fulton - Counties, 1998-2002 (Box 276, Folder 21)
  - Fulton - County, 1991-1993 (Box 276, Folder 22)
  - Fulton (Cities), 1988-1995 (Box 276, Folder 23)
- Fire and Police: Garden City through Glen Cove (Box 277)
  - Garden City (Police), 1975-1993 (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - Garden City (Firefighters + Police Assoc.), 1968-1973 (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - Garden City (Firefighters), 1981-1990 (Box 277, Folder 3)
  - Garden City - villages, 2000-2004 (Box 277, Folder 4)
  - Garden City - Villages, 2000-2004 (Box 277, Folder 5)
  - Garden City (cities), 1972-1997 (Box 277, Folder 6)
  - Gates, 1980-1991 (Box 277, Folder 7)
  - Gates, 1989 (Box 277, Folder 8)
  - Geddes and PBA, 1976-1994 (Box 277, Folder 9)
  - Genesco and AFSME, 1992-1995 (Box 277, Folder 10)
  - Genesee (Policemen), 1972-1987 (Box 277, Folder 11)
  - Genesee Co. Police, 1993-2000 (Box 277, Folder 12)
  - Genesee, 1988-1990 (Box 277, Folder 13)
  - Geneseo - villages, 1995-1998 (Box 277, Folder 14)
  - Geneva - Police, 1970-1996 (Box 277, Folder 15)
  - Geneva (Cities), 1999-2001 (Box 277, Folder 16)
  - Geneva (Police), 1971-1972 (Box 277, Folder 17)
  - Geneva (Firemen), 1969-1971 (Box 277, Folder 18)
  - Geneva (Firemen), 1976-1991 (Box 277, Folder 19)
  - Rubber Workers Geneva, 1990 (Box 277, Folder 20)
  - Glencove (Police), 1971-1974 (Box 277, Folder 21)
  - Glen Cove - city, 1990-1992 (Box 277, Folder 22)
  - Glen Cove (Police), 1975-1985 (Box 277, Folder 23)
- Fire and Police: Glens Falls through Greece (Box 278)
  - Glens Falls (Firemen), 1975-1978 (Box 278, Folder 1)
  - Glens Falls (Cities), 1990-2001 (Box 278, Folder 2)
  - Glens Falls (Police), 1969-1971 (Box 278, Folder 3)
  - Glens Falls (Firemen), 1976-1992 (Box 278, Folder 4)
  - Glens Falls, 1986-1991 (Box 278, Folder 5)
  - Glenville (Police), 1975-1980 (Box 278, Folder 6)
  - Glenville, 1993-1996 (Box 278, Folder 7)
  - Gloversville (Firefighters), 1969-1982 (Box 278, Folder 8)
  - Gloversville (Police), 1984-1986 (Box 278, Folder 9)
  - Gloversville (Firemen), 1969-1979 (Box 278, Folder 10)
  - Gloversville (Police), 1970-1971 (Box 278, Folder 11)
  - Gloversville, 1992 (Box 278, Folder 12)
  - Goshen, village of (Police), 1981-1999 (Box 278, Folder 13)
  - Gouverneur - village, 1968-1982 (Box 278, Folder 14)
  - Gouverneur, village of (Police), 1980-1986 (Box 278, Folder 15)